From: NAT BUNRA

Sangkat Teok Thla, Khan Sen Sok,

Phnom Penh, Cambodia

Tel: (+855) 90 9999 72 / 98 70 66 99

E-mail: natbunra99@gmail.com

To: Apply for Recruitment Position

Having accepted the vacancy from your announcement, I am interested in this announcement. I had

written this letter and my curriculum vitae for a position of **Recruitment Position**. I want to join HR

Team of your company for its qualification appropriate to my skills. As you see my curriculum

vitae, I hope that you will interest in me. I'm comfortable with speaking such as English. Throughout

working as Recruitment Supervisor and Senior HR Officer, I feel confident in my experience and

ability to work.

When I was a Senior HR/Admin Officer, I needed to manage many things such as recruitment

process, monitor on updating job posting with internal and external web pages, manage saving and

screening CVs data base, manage interview schedule with department Manager, conduct interview

candidate, shortlist candidate, reference check, and release job offer.

The kind of work in which your company announced was interest me. Because of the experiences

above, I think I have enough ability to handle this position as well. Moreover, I have got Certificate of

the Best Head Office Employee of the month in GL FINANCE Plc. So I would welcome to the

opportunity to be a staff in your company to contribute my knowledge to the next generations.

I am looking forward to an opportunity to be interviewed and I would be very happy to attend an

interview at any convenient times to you, and you could contact me by my phone number.

Thank you very much for your consideration to my application form!

Sincerely Yours

**NAT BUNRA** 

# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

నువును 🗍 సొసిసాసా

# **NAT BUNRA**

Sangkat Teok Thla, Khan Sen Sok,

Penh, Cambodia

Tel: (+855) 90 9999 72 / 98 70 66 99

E-mail: natbunra99@gmail.com



## PERSONAL INFORMATION

Nationality : Cambodian

Sex : Male

Date of Birth : September 13, 1985

Place of Birth : Kandal Province

Nationality : Khmer
Religion : Buddhist
Marital Status : Married

#### **POSITION APPLIED:**

Senior HR

## **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

2005-2009 : Bachelor of Business Administration as in English for Communication

Norton University, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

2002- 2005 : Student at Hun Sen Ang Snuol High School 1999- 2002 : Student at Beung Thom Secondary School

## **QUALIFICATION**

Sep, 2017 : Certificate of Strategic Recruitment and Staff Onboarding

July, 2015 : Certificate of Best Head Office Employee of the month

April, 2015 : Certificate of the Best HR Practices

Feb, 2012 : Certificate of Call Center Best Employee of the month

June, 2011 : Certificate of Responding to Conflict

Nov, 2011 : Certificate of Effective Communication Skills

August, 2009 : Certificate of STATEGIC CUSTOMER MANAGEMENT

July, 2008 : Certificate of PERSONAL SUCCESS SKILLS

Sep, 2008 : Certificate of ENGLISH LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

## TRAINING COURSES:

Feb-Mar, 2006 : Completed a course in Microsoft Word & Excel

July, 2012 : Certificate of Microsoft Advance Excel 2010

# **LANGUAGES**

Khmer : Mother tongue

English : Advanced Level of English for Communication

(Good Speaking, Listening and Writing Skill)

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

April, 2018 – Present : Western International School, Phnom Penh, Cambodia

# **HR Supervisor-Recruitment**

 Supervises section staff to ensure that they are appropriately motivated and trained and carry out their responsibilities to the required standards;

- Develops and oversees the implementation of WIS's recruitment strategy to ensure that staffing needs are met;
- Develops and oversees the implementation of all necessary systems and procedures to ensure that the recruitment and selection process operate effectively;
- Supervises the process for the placing of advertisements for both internal and external;
- Negotiates contracts with external advertising and recruitment agencies to secure the most favorable terms for WIS;
- Interviews potential recruits and appoints staff in consultation with the appropriate line managers;
- Oversees all administrative arrangements relating to the recruitment and selection process, including arranging tests and providing suitable arrangements for applicants with special needs;
- Keeps up to date with the latest developments in the field of recruitment and selection.

July, 2015 – April, 2018 : GL FINANCE Plc., Phnom Penh, Cambodia

# Senior HR Officer (Recruitment and Training)

- Manage all Recruitment Process;
- Manage Fixed Duration Contract for new staff;
- Manage staff recruitment process include job posting, facilitating interview appointment and process, phone interview, reference check, and release job offer;
- Manage and update HR filing system, ensuring complete personnel record;
- Update Recruitment Plan with hiring Manager;
- Ensure that accurate job descriptions are in place;
- Coordinate with department managers on the design or revisions the job (JD);
- Ensure the up-to-date job description and it is well communicated to the individual staff;
- Manage Career Talk and make the presentation in University in provinces;
- Make good relationship with University, Church, NGO or Pagoda;
- Identify training needs through survey with employees, customers, managers, etc;
- Design and develop training package: presentation slides, quiz, test, game, handout, and other visual materials:
- Deliver training courses to employees;
- Trainer of the training session for HR Policy;
- Support Home Visit team;
- Provide support in administration task;
- Assist Deputy CEO & Deputy HR & Admin Manager on matters related to HR review, policy updates, and employee relations matters.

Oct, 2014 - July, 2015 : GL FINANCE Plc., Phnom Penh, Cambodia

## **HR & Admin Officer**

- Involving in Recruitment Process.
- Prepare Career Talk.
- Prepare Job Posting.
- Prepare CV of candidate and document for the interview.
- Responsible for recruitment and staff selection.
- Interview candidate.
- Prepare Standard Operation Procedure (SOP), Employment Contract and Scope of Work (SOW) for all staff.
- Keep all staff's personnel file.
- Dealing all issues of the administration works.
- Other duties are assigned from HR & Admin Manager if it is necessary and urgent.

May, 2014 - Oct, 2014 : Advanced Bank of Asia (ABA Bank), Phnom Penh, Cambodia

## **Recruitment Assistant**

- Carry out Recruitment Process.
- Job posting.
- Save CV and Screen CV.
- Interview candidate.
- Reference check.
- Draw up job offer letters and contracts.
- Body for a new comer.
- Other duties are assigned from Head of HR if it is necessary and urgent.

Sep, 2013 - May, 2014 : Phnom Penh, Sotelco (Beeline) Co., Ltd, Phnom Penh, Cambodia Sales Specialist

- Warm well coming to customer.
- Assigning SIM Card.
- Releasing new SIM and changed SIM.
- Barring or suspended number.
- Changing of ownership.

Nov, 2009 - Sep, 2013 : Phnom Penh, Sotelco (Beeline) Co., Ltd, Phnom Penh, Cambodia Call Center Specialist

- Managing customers' phone information requires.
- Providing the right information to subscribers.
- Understanding well about product and service.
- Managing customers' retention during phone consultations.
- Participating in user acceptance testing of new products and services.
- Monthly testing of product and service.
- Solve problem with customer concern.
- Target setting by direct manger.

April, 2009 : Completed the INTERNSHIP as an Administrator at Norton University

2008-2009 : Phnom Penh, Hello American School

A part-time teacher of English at Hello American School

2003-2008 : Phnom Penh, Cambodian Volunteer for Community Development

A part-time teacher of English at CVCD

# **HOBIES & INTERESTS:**

- Social Network (LinkedIn & Facebook)

- Reading (Self-Improvement Books)
- Sport (Volleyball & Football)

# **REFERENCES:**

Reference will be provided upon request.